Jyoti Sharma (1) Featured

Fresher seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, System Analysis, Technical, Architecture, Requirement Gathering, Process Improvement, Project Engineering, Agile Methodology, C, C++, HTML, CSS, Java



Current Designation: Java Developer Total Experience: 1 Year(s) 2 Month(s)

Current Company: Oracle Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Kurukshetra Highest Degree: M.Tech [Computers]

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Gurgaon, Delhi / NCR Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, System Analysis, Technical

Architecture, Requirement Gathering, Process Improvement, Project Engineering, Agile

Methodology, C, C++, HTML, CSS, Java, Fresher, Core Java

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Summary

Diligent, ambitious and self-esteemed engineering fresher bringing an excellent foundation of academic success and one year internship experience. Aiming to contribute value to the company through an excellent work ethic and voracious thirst for knowledge.

Work Experience

Oracle as Java Developer Jan 2021 to Till Date

Oracle as Java Developer Jun 2019 to Sep 2020

I have worked on different jira ids and solved more than 65 bugs in different versions of xstore database and also maintain the flow of the operation chain of different XML and java files and also maintain the sequence of xstore data dictionary.

Oracle as Java Developer Jun 2019 to Oct 2020

I have worked on different jira ids and solved more than 65 bugs in different versions of xstore database in Oracle India Pvt Ltd and also maintain the flow of the operation chain in different versions of xstore team.

Oracle as Java Developer Jun 2019 to Aug 2020

I have worked on different jira id and solve more than 65 bugs and provide my inputs to solve the different problems in different versions of xstore team and also manage the data dictionary of xstore database.

1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=31602fce4ded0aa0827e455723ac330d505c0d0342125c40064714585e...

Oracle as Java Developer Jun 2019 to Sep 2020

I have worked on different jira ids and solved more than 65 bugs in different versions of xstore team and also maintain the data dictionary of xstore database

Oracle India Pvt. Ltd. as Java Developer

Jun 2019 to Sep 2020

I have worked on different jira ids and solved more than 65 bugs in different versions of xstore database in Oracle and also maintain the flow of the data dictionary of xstore database.

Oracle as Java Developer Jun 2019 to Sep 2020

I have worked on different jira ids and solve more than 65 bugs in different versions of xstore team and also maintain the flow of the opchain and XML sequence in the required database.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Seth Jai Prakash Mukund Lal Institute of Engineering and Technology, Yamunanagar in 2018

PG: M.Tech (Computers) from Thapar Institute of Engineering and Technology (TIET) in 2020

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Oracle internship

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
JAVA	
HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT	
Oracle database-SQL	
C, C++	
Agile ,Jira Methodology	

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time